A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13 FA285
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Old Book Program - Authors Files, 5
  - Winters, Robert W. - "Energy and Protein Metabolism of the Human Infant", October 7, 1975-June 1, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 534)
  - Wise, Harold B. - Neighborhood Medical Care Demonstration, February 18, 1969-August 14, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 535)
  - Wolf, Stewart - "An Anatomy of Health: The Roseto Story", February 5-27, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 536)
  - Wolfe, Richard J. - "The Alexander Forbes Papers", June 6, 1978-December 10, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 537)
- Out-of-Print Publications, 6
  The folders are arranged alphabetically by book; however, part of this subseries is missing so that the books only go as far as the Ds.
  The sixth subseries is concerned with the publishing of certain books. The subseries consists of correspondence and financial papers with publishing companies and involves such publishing matters as bindings, engravings and jackets. The documents date mostly from the 1920s to the 1940s. Some of these books are reviewed in the subseries Reviews.
  - "Administration of Workmen's Compensation", February 1, 1936-November 14, 1946 (Box 50, Folder 538)
  - "Administration Control of Aliens" (William C. Van Vleck), April 6, 1931-November 1, 1937 (Box 50, Folder 539)
  - "Administrative Powers over Persons and Property", August 11, 1927-May 21, 1959 (Box 51, Folder 540)
  - "Adult Intelligence", November 12, 1934-June 23, 1936 (Box 51, Folder 541)
  - "American Hospital" (B-F), January 18, 1946-July 7, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 542)
  - "American Hospital" (G-W), January 28, 1946-September 25, 1946 (Box 51, Folder 543)
  - "The Approach to the Parent" (Esther Heath), June 17, 1932-November 5, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 544)
  - "The Attendant's Guide" (A-C), May 12, 1943-April 17, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 545)
  - "The Attendant's Guide" (C-H), March 29, 1945-October 26, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 546)
  - "The Attendant's Guide" (L-M), January 29, 1945-June 18, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 547)
  - "The Attendant's Guide" (N-S), October 30, 1944-December 21, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 548)
  - "Bacteriology of Typhoid, Salmonella, and Dysentery Infections and Carrier States" (Leon C. Havens), May 22, 1933-October 11, 1938 (Box 51, Folder 549)
  - "The Baker Memorial", February 25, 1941-July 25, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 550)
  - "Borrowed Children", June 5, 1940-November 9, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 551)
  - "Changes in the Knee Joint at Various Ages", November 26, 1938-May 25, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 552)
  - "Chapter of Child Health", October 8, 1929-April 30, 1930 (Box 52, Folder 553)
  - "Child Guidance Cases" (Mary B. Sayles) (B-P), May 22, 1929-May 26, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 554)
  - "Child Guidance Cases" (Mary B. Sayles) (B-P), May 22, 1929-May 26, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 555)
  - "Child Guidance Clinics" (B-C), June 1, 1928-March 10, 1944 (Box 52, Folder 556)
  - "Child Guidance Clinics" (D-T), March 19, 1934-October 20, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 557)
  - "Child Health and the Community" (Courtenay Dinwiddie), April 28, 1928-June 2, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 558)
  - "Children at the Crossroads" (Agnes E. Benedict), November 13, 1929-August 31, 1932 (Box 52, Folder 559)
  - "Children Handicapped by Cerebral Palsy", June 18, 1936-May 14, 1946 (Box 52, Folder 560)
  - "Children of the Covered Wagon", July 29, 1929-November 9, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 561)
  - "Children's Behavior and Teacher's Attitude", September 23, 1976-October 4, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 562)
  - "Clinical Significance of the Blood in Tuberculosis" (Gulli Lindh Muller), November 11, 1941-May 5, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 563)
  - "Commonwealth Fund Activities in Austria" (William J. French and Geddes Smith), April 18, 1930-November 12, 1930 (Box 53, Folder 564)
  - "Commonwealth Fund Fellows and Their Impression of America", February 11, 1932-August 31, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 565)
  - "Community Health Organization" (B-J), April 29, 1932-March 20, 1951 (Box 53, Folder 566)
  - "Community Health Organization" (J-W), February 6, 1939-April 6, 1954 (Box 53, Folder 567)
  - "Criminal Careers in Retrospect", June 4, 1943-January 19, 1944 (Box 53, Folder 568)
  - "Criminal Youth and the Borstal System", March 20, 1947-September 2, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 569)
  - "Cross-Sections of Rural Health Progress", September 7, 1928-November 22, 1937 (Box 53, Folder 570)
  - "Directory of Psychiatric Clinics", May 15, 1928-March 8, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 571)
  - Distribution of Publications, November 1936-July 1941 (Box 53, Folder 572)
  - Distribution of Publications, November 1936-July 1941 (Box 53, Folder 573)
  - Distribution of Publications, November 1936-July 1941 (Box 53, Folder 574)
  - Distribution of Publications, August 1941-July 1945 (Box 54, Folder 575)
  - Distribution of Publications, August 1941-July 1945 (Box 54, Folder 576)
  - Distribution of Publications, August 1941-July 1945 (Box 54, Folder 577)
  - "The Doctor and the Difficult Child" (B-K), October 28, 1940-March 12, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 578)
  - "The Doctor and the Difficult Child" (L-R), August 8, 1940-February 20, 1951 (Box 54, Folder 579)
- Publications (Adm-h Files), 7
  The seventh subseries consists of the Division's administrative correspondence. The subseries has been divided into six sections: Authors, Complimentary Distribution to Medical Schools and Libraries, Permission to Quote, Permission to Reprint, Permission to Translate, and Publishing. The correspondence is concerned with matters relating to the titles and dates from the 1940s to the 1970s.
  - Authors - Brigham Hospital, Peter Bent - "Intern-Resident Training", June 28, 1946-October 28, 1947 (Box 54, Folder 580)
  - Authors - Horowitz, Milton - "Patterns of Learning in Medical Students", June 22, 1960-June 22, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 581)
  - Authors - Levy, S. William and Gilbert H. Barnes - "Skin Problems of the Amputee", April 17, 1964-June 1, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 582)
  - Authors - Morton, Roy J. - "Sanitation Practice in Local Health Departments", May 7, 1942-July 2, 1957 (Box 54, Folder 583)
  - Authors - Morton, Roy J. - "Sanitation Practice in Local Health Departments", May 7, 1942-July 2, 1957 (Box 54, Folder 584)
  - Authors - Shen, James K., May 8, 1946-June 30, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 585)
  - Authors - Silverman, Samuel - "Psychophysical Aspects of Illness", September 17, 1964-April 7, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 586)
  - Authors - Upjohn Company - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart", September 26, 1949-October 6, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 587)
  - Authors - Wilson, Robert N. - "Process Analysis: A Study of Community Structure and Health Action", 1966 (Box 55, Folder 588)
  - Authors - Wilson, Robert N. - "Process Analysis: A Study of Community Structure and Health Action", 1966 (Box 55, Folder 589)
  - Authors - Yett, Donald E. - "The Development of A Micro-Simulation Model of Health Manpower Demand and Supply", August 1, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 590)
  - Authors - Yett, Donald E. - "The Development of A Micro-Simulation Model of Health Manpower Demand and Supply", August 1, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 591)
  - Authors - Yett, Donald E. - "The Development of A Micro-Simulation Model of Health Manpower Demand and Supply", August 1, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 592)
  - Complimentary Distribution to Medical Schools and Libraries - General Correspondence, March 18, 1954-April 16, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 593)
  - Complimentary Distribution to Medical Schools and Libraries - General Correspondence, March 18, 1954-April 16, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 594)
  - Complimentary Distribution to Medical Schools and Libraries - General Correspondence, March 18, 1954-April 16, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 595)
  - Complimentary Distribution to Medical Schools and Libraries (A-M), 1965 (Box 56, Folder 596)
  - Complimentary Distribution to Medical Schools and Libraries (N-Z), 1965 (Box 56, Folder 597)
  - Complimentary Distribution to Medical Schools and Libraries (A-Z), 1966 (Box 56, Folder 598)
  - Complimentary Distribution to Medical Schools and Libraries - Responses to Roger A. Crane, February 20, 1958-April 24, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 599)
  - Permission to Quote - Authors Listing (A-C), July 13, 1949-November 9, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 600)
  - Permission to Quote - Authors Listing (D-J), May 28, 1946-April 9, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 601)
  - Permission to Quote - Authors Listing (K-M), October 30, 1944-November 28, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 602)
  - Permission to Quote - Authors Listing (N-R), June 4, 1946-May 26, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 603)
  - Permission to Quote - Authors Listing (S-V), January 26, 1944-November 15, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 604)
  - Permission to Quote - Authors Listing (W-Z), November 21, 1949-June 5, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 605)
  - Permission to Quote - General Correspondence, June 19, 1951-June 11, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 606)
  - Permission to Quote - General Correspondence, June 19, 1951-June 11, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 607)
  - Permission to Quote - Paul, Benjamin, March 18, 1955-November 4, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 608)
  - Permission to Quote - Thomas, Charles C., March 29, 1945-November 3, 1949 (Box 57, Folder 609)
  - Permission to Quote - Williams, Ralph C., November 22-27, 1950 (Box 57, Folder 610)
  - Permission to Quote - Wright, Samson, May 4, 1950-February 23, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 611)
  - Permission to Reprint - General Correspondence, May 21, 1969-October 4, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 612)
  - Permission to Reprint - Harvard University Press - General Correspondence (A-H), January 25, 1951-June 11, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 613)
  - Permission to Reprint - Harvard University Press - General Correspondence (I-Z), August 15, 1951-April 16, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 614)
  - Permission to Reprint - Harvard University Press - Microfilms, September 23, 1958-August 4, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 615)
  - Permission to Reprint - Patterson Smith Publishing Corporation, January 5, 1969-December 8, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 616)
  - Permission to Reprint - Ransom, Donald C. - "Patients Have Families", February 9, 1972-December 22, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 617)
  - Permission to Reprint - Somers, Anne R. - The Kaiser-Permanente Medical Care Program, A Symposium, June 20, 1974-August 29, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 618)
  - Permission to Translate - "Attendant's Guide", January 12-26, 1949 (Box 58, Folder 619)
  - Permission to Translate - "Bacteriology of Typhoid, Salmonella and Dysentery", April 1, 1947-June 9, 1947 (Box 58, Folder 620)
  - Permission to Translate - "Chemotherapy and Serum Therapy of Pneumonia", December 6, 1940-December 22, 1941 (Box 58, Folder 621)
  - Permission to Translate - "Child Health Demonstration Bulletin", August 16-22, 1935 (Box 58, Folder 622)
  - Permission to Translate - "Compania General Editora", August 14, 1940-March 9, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 623)
  - Permission to Translate - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart", February 21, 1955-March 21, 1958 (Box 58, Folder 624)
  - Permission to Translate - "Cross Sections of Rural Health Practices", June 4, 1935-March 13, 1942 (Box 58, Folder 625)
  - Permission to Translate - General Correspondence, March 14, 1950-May 15, 1957 (Box 58, Folder 626)
  - Permission to Translate - Harvard University Press - General Correspondence, August 27, 1951-June 30, 1964 (Box 58, Folder 627)
  - Permission to Translate - "Hypertension and Hypertensive Disease", October 16-18, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 628)
  - Permission to Translate - "Introduction to Group Therapy", October 7, 1948-April 27, 1951 (Box 58, Folder 629)
  - Permission to Translate - "Librarie Rombaldi", November 9-16, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 630)
  - Permission to Translate - "Mental Illness", February 6, 1946-May 8, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 631)
  - Permission to Translate - "Microbial Antagonisms and Antibiotic Substance", May 27, 1946-November 22, 1950 (Box 58, Folder 632)
  - Permission to Translate - "Organizing for a Child Guidance Clinic", June 30, 1943-July 2, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 633)
  - Permission to Translate - "Physiology of the Nervous System", February 5, 1941 (Box 58, Folder 634)
  - Permission to Translate - "Psychiatric Clinic for Children", March 14, 1945-November 16, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 635)
  - Permission to Translate - "Public Health Laws", July 28, 1943-January 2, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 636)
  - Permission to Translate - "Public Health Nurse", October 28-30, 1947 (Box 58, Folder 637)
  - Permission to Translate - "Red Cell and Case Developments", April 4, 1964-July 21, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 638)
  - Permission to Translate - "Rural Health Practices", February 15, 1939-October 18, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 639)
  - Permission to Translate - "Science Service", August 24, 1944-January 16, 1949 (Box 58, Folder 640)
  - Permission to Translate - "Supervision in Public Health Work", December 19, 1949-March 30, 1951 (Box 58, Folder 641)
  - Permission to Translate - "Teaching and Learning in Medical School", June 20, 1961-September 8, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 642)
  - Permission to Translate - "Tutoring as Therapy", January 12-23, 1947 (Box 58, Folder 643)
  - Publishing - Acknowledgement of Free Books, February 6, 1966-June 1, 1966 (Box 58, Folder 644)
  - Publishing - Basic Book Service, December 3, 1952-June 12, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 645)
  - Publishing - Commonwealth Fund Authors, July 18, 1935-January 28, 1952 (Box 58, Folder 646)
  - Publishing - Connecticut Printers, June 18, 1953-December 2, 1958 (Box 58, Folder 647)
  - Publishing - Connecticut Printers, February 27, 1959-June 4, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 648)
  - Publishing - Division of Publications - Inventory, November 9, 1948-May 22, 1951 (Box 59, Folder 649)
  - Publishing - Division of Publications - Lists of Cuts, Coated Sheets and Illustrations, August 11, 1950-June 18, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 650)
  - Publishing - Harper and Row Publishers, Inc., January 3, 1962-July 15, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 651)
  - Publishing - Harvard University Press - Brochures and Printing, August 20, 1971-October 19, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 652)
  - Publishing - Harvard University Press - General Correspondence, February 2, 1953-July 8, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 653)
  - Publishing - Harvard University Press - Out-of-Print, September 18, 1969-July 25, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 654)
  - Publishing - Harvard University Press - Publication Schedule, December 8, 1970-October 7, 1971 (Box 59, Folder 655)
  - Publishing - Harvard University Press - Reviews, December 18, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 656)
  - Publishing - Harvard University Press - Staff (Orlov, Ann), August 18, 1969-April 17, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 657)
  - Publishing - Harvard University Press - Staff (Stratton, Burton L.), July 10, 1951-October 9, 1967 (Box 59, Folder 658)
  - Publishing - Harvard University Press - Staff (Wilson, Thomas J.), September 4, 1953-June 30, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 659)
  - Publishing - Photo Engraving, November 13, 1959-September 4, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 660)
  - Publishing - Publishing Program on Medical Education or Medical Research, September 30, 1953-June 13, 1955 (Box 59, Folder 661)
- Reviews, 8
  The folders are arranged alphabetically by book.
  This subseries consists of newspapers and journal articles about various Commonwealth Fund Books. These articles are reviews of certain books. The folders date mostly from the 1940s to the 1960s. The books reviewed can be found in the Out-of-Print Publications and Titles subseries.
  - "Advances in Rheumatic Fever", January 1963-May 25, 1963 (Box 59, Folder 662)
  - "Adventures in Medical Education", February 1, 1958-November 7, 1958 (Box 59, Folder 663)
  - "Airborne Contagion", May 14, 1955-May 22, 1959 (Box 59, Folder 664)
  - "Airborne Infection", July 10, 1943-August 29, 1961 (Box 59, Folder 665)
  - "American Medical Practice", December 20, 1940-April 30, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 666)
  - "American Medical Research, Past and Present", December 15, 1947-April 1951 (Box 60, Folder 667)
  - Annual Report, January 24, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 668)
  - "Atlas of Exfoliative Cytology", March 1954-April 1962 (Box 60, Folder 669)
  - "Atlas of Exfoliative Cytology", March 1954-April 1962 (Box 60, Folder 670)
  - "Atlas of the Blood in Children", December 20, 1944-1950 (Box 60, Folder 671)
  - "Brucellosis in Man and Animals", 1939-1949 (Box 60, Folder 672)
  - "Brucellosis in Man and Animals", 1939-1949 (Box 60, Folder 673)
  - "Cancer in Families", July 6, 1959-September 29, 1960 (Box 60, Folder 674)
  - "Cardiac Catheterization in Congenital Heart Disease", April 1949-January 29, 1957 (Box 60, Folder 675)
  - "Case Development Problems in Hematology", July 1963-October 1963 (Box 60, Folder 676)
  - "Changes in the Knee Joint at Various Ages", November 7, 1942-May 1946 (Box 60, Folder 677)
  - "Child Health Services and Pediatric Education", April 13, 1949-September 28, 1953 (Box 60, Folder 678)
  - "Childhood Schizophrenia", February 23, 1962-October 1963 (Box 60, Folder 679)
  - "Children Handicapped by Cerebral Palsy", March 20, 1937-January 1949 (Box 60, Folder 680)
  - "Chronic Illness in the U. S." (Volume I: Prevention of Chronic Illness), December 1957-January 1959 (Box 60, Folder 681)
  - "Chronic Illness in the U. S." (Volume II: Care of the Long Term Patient), September 1956-July 12, 1958 (Box 60, Folder 682)
  - "Chronic Illness in the U. S." (Volume III: Chronic Illness in a Rural Area-Hunterdon Study), March 1960-December 1961 (Box 60, Folder 683)
  - "Chronic Illness in the U. S." (Volume IV: Chronic Illness in a Large City-Baltimore Study), June 1957-March 7, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 684)
  - "Closed Ranks: An Experiment in Mental Health Education", August 1957-January 1960 (Box 60, Folder 685)
  - Commonwealth Fund - Historical Sketch, May 1963 (Box 60, Folder 686)
  - "Community Health Organization", August 11, 1932-1952 (Box 61, Folder 687)
  - "Community Programs for Mental Health", September 17, 1955-April 1957 (Box 61, Folder 688)
  - "Congenital Malformations of the Heart", June 5, 1947 to November 1, 1954; March 25, 1961 to September 1962 (Box 61, Folder 689)
  - "Congenital Malformations of the Heart", June 5, 1947 to November 1, 1954; March 25, 1961 to September 1962 (Box 61, Folder 690)
  - "Coronary Heart Disease in Young Adults", July 10, 1954-February 1957 (Box 61, Folder 691)
  - "Cousins and Strangers", March 1956-March 2, 1957 (Box 61, Folder 692)
  - "Dentistry", September 21, 1946-1949 (Box 61, Folder 693)
  - "Diagnosis of Cancer", August 1943-May 13, 1948 (Box 61, Folder 694)
  - "Doctor and Difficult Child", December 21, 1940-January 1949 (Box 61, Folder 695)
  - "Doctor and Difficult Child" (Revised Edition), November 15, 1947-April 1950 (Box 61, Folder 696)
  - "Ecology of Health", December 17, 1949-April 1951 (Box 61, Folder 697)
  - "Effect of Advancing Age Upon the Human Spinal Cord", April 11, 1959-August 1960 (Box 61, Folder 698)
  - "The Envelope", January 1950-1952 (Box 61, Folder 699)
  - "Epithelia of Woman's Reproductive Organs", February 16, 1948-1952 (Box 61, Folder 700)
  - "Explorations into the Nature of the Living Cell", August 22, 1961-February 1963 (Box 61, Folder 701)
  - "Foster Home Care", September 1944-April 1956 (Box 61, Folder 702)
  - "Foundations for Science of Personality", 1952 (Box 61, Folder 703)
  - "Functional Endocrinology, From Birth Through Adolescence", October 16, 1952-September 1953 (Box 62, Folder 704)
  - "Fundamentals of Roentgenology", September 3, 1964-October 29, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 705)
  - "Future for Preventive Medicine", December 10, 1945-November 1947 (Box 62, Folder 706)
  - "Genetic Basis of Morphological Variation", June 1960-March 1962 (Box 62, Folder 707)
  - "Government in Public Health", July 1940-1950 (Box 62, Folder 708)
  - "Group Psychotherapy", May 1953-February 1956 (Box 62, Folder 709)
  - "Health and Medical Care in New York City" (Health Insurance Plan), April 1957-June 1960 (Box 62, Folder 710)
  - "Health Center Buildings", April 1957-June 1960 (Box 62, Folder 711)
  - "Health Insurance in the U.S.A.", Decemer 3, 1946-1950 (Box 62, Folder 712)
  - "Heredity in Uterine Cancer", March 8, 1952-1962 (Box 62, Folder 713)
  - "Hospital Care in the United States", December 1945-May 1958 (Box 62, Folder 714)
  - "Hospital Trends and Developments", May 1948-February 1950 (Box 62, Folder 715)
  - "Hunterdon Medical Center", May 12, 1956-January 1958 (Box 62, Folder 716)
  - "Hypertension", August 5, 1944-February 1947 (Box 62, Folder 717)
  - "Introduction to Universal Serologic Reaction", April 3, 1951-March 21, 1953 (Box 62, Folder 718)
  - "Juvenile Delinquents Grown Up", May 2, 1940-1944 (Box 62, Folder 719)
  - "Liberal Arts and Medical Education", May 5, 1958 (Box 62, Folder 720)
  - "Local Health Units", March 1945-May 12, 1948 (Box 63, Folder 721)
  - "Longitudinal Studies of Child Personality", November 1959-April 1961 (Box 63, Folder 722)
  - "Maternal Mortality in New York City", April 12, 1930-October 13, 1938 (Box 63, Folder 723)
  - "Maternity Care in Two Counties", October 1950-August 1951 (Box 63, Folder 724)
  - "The Meaning of Social Medicine", May 24, 1954-February 1956 (Box 63, Folder 725)
  - "Medical Addenda", July 12, 1947-January 1949 (Box 63, Folder 726)
  - "Medial Care of the Discharged Hospital Patient", February 29, 1944-November 1948 (Box 63, Folder 727)
  - "Medical Education and Changing Order", June 26, 1946-May 1951 (Box 63, Folder 728)
  - "Medical Services by Government", May 28, 1946-1952 (Box 63, Folder 729)
  - "Medical Services for Rural Areas", August 1956-January 1958 (Box 63, Folder 730)
  - "Medicine in Industry", April 23, 1946-April 30, 1948 (Box 63, Folder 731)
  - "Medicine in the Changing Order", February 1947-January 1950 (Box 63, Folder 732)
  - "Mental Health in Modern Society", 1946-April 1956 (Box 63, Folder 733)
  - "Mental Health in the U.S.: A Fifty Year History", May 8, 1961-November 1963 (Box 63, Folder 734)
  - "Metabolic Homoeostasis", November 1960-January 7, 1961 (Box 63, Folder 735)
  - "Metabolic Response to Neonatal Surgery", July 25, 1957-July 28, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 736)
  - "Milk and Food Sanitation Practice", June 7, 1947-January 1950 (Box 64, Folder 737)
  - Miscellaneous Book Reviews, July 1963-April 6, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 738)
  - "Modern Attack on Tuberculosis", May 1942-December 1948 (Box 64, Folder 739)
  - "Mosquito Control", April 1940-August 1946 (Box 64, Folder 740)
  - "Negroes and Medicine", December 26, 1958-June 1961 (Box 64, Folder 741)
  - "Nursing and Nursing Education", March 18, 1946-April 1948 (Box 64, Folder 742)
  - "Nursing in Industry", February 1946-January 3, 1948 (Box 64, Folder 743)
  - "Office Management for Health Workers", June 14, 1949-June 4, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 744)
  - "Organized Home Medical Care in New York City", October 19, 1956-September 1960 (Box 64, Folder 745)
  - "Patients Have Families", January 11, 1945-October 8, 1952 (Box 64, Folder 746)
  - "Pediatric Psychiatry", December 7, 1963 (Box 64, Folder 747)
  - "Pediatrics and the Emotional Needs of the Child", October 6, 1948-January 8, 1952 (Box 64, Folder 748)
  - "Perinatal Mortality in New York City", June 5, 1955-January 10, 1958 (Box 64, Folder 749)
  - "Personality and The Cultural Pattern", April 29, 1937-October 1946 (Box 64, Folder 750)
  - "Physiology of Shock", March 1951-1954 (Box 65, Folder 751)
  - "The Pineal Gland", December 1954-April 27, 1956 (Box 65, Folder 752)
  - "Plague on Us", January 11, 1941-May 15, 1947 (Box 65, Folder 753)
  - "Plague on Us", January 11, 1941-May 15, 1947 (Box 65, Folder 754)
  - "Poliomyelitis", April 1942-November 1945 (Box 65, Folder 755)
  - "The Practical Nurse", May 1945-May 28, 1953 (Box 65, Folder 756)
  - "Prevention of Chronic Illness", September 1957-April 1958 (Box 65, Folder 757)
  - "Prothrombin", November 17, 1962-August 1, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 758)
  - "Psychiatric Clinics for Children", n.d. (Box 65, Folder 759)
  - "Psychiatric Hospital As A Small Society", December 1958-February 1961 (Box 65, Folder 760)